< front-end developer />

I am a self-taught front-end developer. I gained my first experience in this position at the Webiso Interactive Agency, where I successfully implemented the projects I in charge of. Working with more experienced developers, I was able to improve my skills and expand my knowledge with new technologies. As a freelancer, I created my first commercial projects. I gain the most satisfaction at work when I am challenged, have the opportunity to develop myself and learn new things. My Experience and soft skills acquired at jobs beyond IT branch certainly bring many positive aspects to the team I join. I am open to cooperation on B2B contract or employment contract.



(°) +48 503 58 34 37

- tomaszrysak@o2.pl
- github.com/tomi5
- in linkedin.com/in/tomasz-rysak
- Skawina, woj. małopolskie

Technologies I use:

- HTML 5
- CSS3 (flexbox, grid, BEM)
- Sass
- JavaScript
- React.js
- iQuerv
- Bootstrap 4
- RWD
- Git
- PHP (SMARTY)

I'm learning:

- TypeScript
- GatsbyJS + GraphQL

I want to know:

- Node.js
- MongoDB
- Python

Others Abilities:

- fluent in CorelDraw
- basic in Visual Basis and fluent in Excel
- Photoshop (PSD slicing and basic image processing)
- English upper intermediate
- Polish native speaker
- traveling, extreme and qualified
 tourism
- low cost flight search
- nature photography
- sports: football, muay-thai, cycling, snowboarding
- travel books and magazines
- stock exchange

SELECTED PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Deceber, 2019 - May, 2020 Webiso - Front-End Developer - B2B

- creating websites with HTML, CSS (SASS, Bootstrap), JavaScript and PHP,
- CMS implementations,
- writing and implementing CMS Plugins (PHP, Smarty),
- · maintaining and improving websites,
- getting feedback from users and customers.

March, 2016 - November, 2019 Orlando Travel - travel specialist

- · creating an own offer of group tours and supervising ongoing tours,
- customer acquisition and maintaining good customer relationship,
- acquiring and contacting contractors (mainly in English),
- the originator of the offer of own tourist trips with Dynamic Packing implementation and supervision,
- · website update using CMS.

August, 2013 - March, 2016 Tour Operator - travel specialist

- · creating tailor-made trips,
- supervising ongoing tours organized by the Tour Organizator,
- contact with the customer,
- contact with contractors, price negotiations mainly in English.

OWN PROJECTS

Personal CV

Polish and English version. Adapted to print in A4 page size. Used: React.js

LandLab - commercial project

Commercial website for landscape architecture company.

Used: HTML5 - CSS3 (Sass, flexbox) - JavaScript - CMS (CMS MADE SIMPLE) - PHP (SMARTY) - RWD

Interactive Map of Visited Countries

My first training project to practice JavaScript.

Used: HTML5 - CSS3 (flexbox) - JavaScript - RWD

Single Page - commercial project

Website design and coding. Website prepared for a friend's company.

Used: HTML5 - CSS3 - jQuery - RWD

Travel Service - template

Bootstrap 4 training project.

Used: HTML5 - Bootstrap 4 - jQuery - LightBox

Single Page Template - PSD to HTML

My first RWD single page website converted from PSD.

Used: HTML5 - CSS3 (flexbox) - jQuery - Photoshop (slice tool)

EDUCATION

2007 - 2012 - Jagiellonian University in Krakow

Master's degree in Geography, specialisation in Tourism

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).



CONTACT